Business Ephemera Collection
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library
- Trade cards, Business Cards, Miscellaneous Small Advertisements
  - Trade card, Brown's Grocery House, 1880?; "With an assortment of Choice Groceries, specially designed for the Holiday trade." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Postcard, Brown-Howland Company, 1915; Postcard with portrait of Thomas Edison: "Why have your letters written twice--in shorthand and on the typewriter? Save this time and money; write them once--in typewriting--with the Edison Dictating Machine." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Business card, Brownstone, 1983; "a unique dining experience" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, D.H. Buell, 186-?; Two designs featuring a boy with a drum and a monkey (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, D.H. Buell, 186-?; Two designs featuring yachts in Boston Harbor (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, D.H. Buell, 187-?; Floral design (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, D.H. Buell, 188-?; "The Celebrated Vacheron & Constantin Watch is made by machine, highly finished and adjusted by the best known workmen of Switzerland…." Engraved by John A. Lowell, Boston. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Buick Garage Company, 191-; "Formerly Boardman's Stables" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Burke Brothers, 18--; "Hats & Caps." Three different designs with flowers, birds, butterfly. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Burke Brothers, 18--; "Hats & Caps." Two esigns featuring a boy with a drum and a monkey and a couple in eighteenth-century dress. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, T.F. Burke, 1879? (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Business card, Bushnell, 198-?; "Marie M. Lasher, Group Sales, Children's Theater Co-ordinator (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Brochure, Butler's, 192-; "Let the Ever Ready Charge Account be your Santa Claus" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, S.E. Butterfield and Company, 187-?; "Call and see what a dollar will buy." Card with photograph: "Learning A.B.C." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, M. Cameron, 18--; "Clocks put in order in any part of the City." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Cadden Clothing Company, 188-?; Three designs featuring dogs, cats, and flowers. (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Cadden Clothing Company, 188-?; Two designs featuring deer and flowers. (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Cadden Clothing Company, 188-?; Two designs featuring deer and flowers. (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, R.H. Canfield, 1880? (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Postcard, Capewell Horse Nail Company, 190-?; Postcard serves as order form: "Please send me the following Capewell Horse Nails…. " (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Capitol Shoe Store, 189-?; "Go to G. W. Pomroy's for Good Carriages, Harness and Horses." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, Casa de Puerto Rico, 198-?; Business card of Antonio J. Soto, Excecutive Director. 2 copies. (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Centinel Hill Press, 197-?; Eliot N. Bidwell, Editor (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, Chicago Title Insurance Company, 198-?; Business card of Anna Sica, Customer Service Coordinator (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Clayton H. Case, 1880; Printed by the Calvert Lithographic Company, Detroit, Michigan (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Clayton H. Case, 188-?; "Fine Jewelry -Solid Silver Clocks - Watch Cases Repairing - Platedware Watches." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Clayton H. Case, 188-?; Four different designs (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Clayton H. Case, 188-?; Design features butterfly and flowers (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Bookmark, Clayton H. Case, 188-?; Design features a woman in fancy dress (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, H.H. Case and Company, 189-?; Two different designs: "The 'Minnesota Good News Flour' makes the Whitest and Best Bread and Biscuits." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Orvill P. Case, 186-?; "Extra Family Flour, Crockery, Stone, Wood and Willow Ware, Brass and Wood Clocks." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Case and Daniels, 188-?; "Fine Boots & Shoes." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Postcard, S.D. Chamberlain, 1885; Two copies. Includes price list (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, G.T. Chapman, 188-?; Four designs with figures in fancy dress on gold backgrounds. Printed by Ketterlinus, Philadelphia, Pennsylvanis. (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, G.T. Chapman, 188-?; Two different floral designs (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, G.T. Chapman, 188-?; "First-class Hel0 Furnished for City and Country at Reasonable Rates. Satisfaction Guaranteed!" (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Charter Oak Dining Room, 1871-1872; George W. Pomeroy, Proprietor. "Meals served to order at all hours of the day or evening." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Charter Oak Dining Rooms, 1873-1874; George W. Pomeroy, Proprietor. "Dining Rooms for Ladies & Gentlemen." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, Theresa Chinkowitz, 192-?; "Popular Music - Ragtime - Jazz- Blues and Novelty Piano Playing" (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, City Coal Company, 1905; "Best Domestic Coal." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, City Frame Company, 198- (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, City Garden, 187-?; P. D. Whitmore, Proprietor. "Plants and Flowers sent to any part of the City or Country." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, City Hotel, 1860?; W. W. Moore, C. Ticknor, Proprietors (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, City Sewing Center, 1960?; Jack Becker, Manager (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Clark and Caswell, 187-?; "Examine Denham's Patent Shirt." Five different floral designs. (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, George N. Clark and Company, 188-?; "Old Stand of Dr. John Braddock" (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Theodore Clark (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Theodore Clark, 187-? (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Clay Hill Bicycle Shop, 19--; J. D'Emilio, Proprietor. "New Low Prices on Bicycles, Velocipedes, Scooter Bikes and Accessories." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Collum & Bryant, 1876; Two different designs, one printed by Ketterlinus, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, Cololt Industrial Park, 198-?; Business card of Roy W. Orbell, General Manager (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, Commodore Hotel, 191-?; Meyer Reichlin, Manager. "Near Railroad Station and Bus Terminals." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, Congress rotisserie, 198-?; Restaurant, Carry Out, Catering, Delivery Service (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, H.W. Conklin, 188-?; Two cards with views of Hudson River and California Coast (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, H.W. Conklin, 188-?; Four different floral designs (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, H.W. Conklin, 188-?; Three designs with children and flowers (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, H.W. Conklin, 188-?; Three designs with figures in eighteenth-century costume (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, H.W. Conklin, 188-?; Three designs with Japanese women (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, H.W. Conklin, 187-?; Three cards printed by the Eureka Printing Company, New Haven, Connecticut (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, H.W. Conklin, 18--?; "Do you want Comfort? Do you desire Style? Do you wish Quality? Then buy the Patent Detached Bosom Shirt." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, H.W. Conklin, 187-?; Four designs featuring children (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, Connecticut National Guard, 18--?; Business card of Herbert W. Thompson, Company "F," First Regiment. (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, Connecticut National Guard, 18--?; Business Card of Clarence H. Wickham, Company "F," First Regiment. Two different designs. (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, State of Connecticut - Department of Health Services, 198-?; Business card of Hector Seda, Preventable Diseases Division, Aids Education Specialist (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, State of Connecticut - State Attorney's Office, 198-?; Business card of Charles A. Lexius, Victim/Witness Advocate (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, D.P. Cook, 187-?; Two designs featuring animals (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, D.P. Cook, 188-?; Two different designs: "North side of the New Post Office" (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Miss Cook's Millinery Rooms, 187-?; Two different designs: "North side of the New Post Office" (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, John Coombs, 187-?; "Floral Designs and Cut Flowers" (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Postcard, Coombs, 190-?; "Twenty-Six Large Greenhouses" "Artistic Floral Designs made at short notice." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, J.H. and W.E. Cone, 190-?; "Sole Agent for Tremont Percha Steel Nails." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, L.D. Corbin, 187-? (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Truman Cowles, 18--; "Orders taken and delivered in any part of the city." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Henry Cowlishaw, 188-?; "Sissors, Shears, Cuttlery and Lawn Mowers Ground and Repaired. Hand-forging and Tempering Done." Eight designs featuring presidents of the United States. (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Wm. Crane, 189-?; "The Silo Man, Representing The B. L. Bragg Co. Springfield, Mass." (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Business card, Creative Cakes by Donna, 198-?; Donna Everett and Helen Whitcher, Proprietors. "Elegant, Unique, Moist Wedding Cakes Creatively Designed with Fresh Flowers" (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, Crittenden and Southwick, 186-?; L. S. Crittenden and D. F. Southwick, Proprietors (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, John Curley, 18-- (Box 8, Folder C)
  - Trade card, W.H.H. Daggett, 189- (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Danforth, Church and Company, 18--; J. W. Danforth, George Church, William H. Danforth, Proprietors (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Daniels and Holbrook, 18--; Printed by J. H. Bufford's Sons, Boston & New York. (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Postcard, Daniels Cadillac Oldsmobile, Inc., 1963 (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Day, Caswell and Company, 1865-1872; "The Only One Price Clothing Store in Hartford." (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, R.S. De Lamater, 18--; Two different cards, each with a profile portrait of a woman, one signed "Anderson" and one signed "Favart." (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Postcard, Deming and Gundlach, 1859?; "Watches of all kinds repaired in the best manner and warranted to run well." (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Postcard, Deming and Gundlach, 188-?; Card in the shape of a keystone advertising Keystone Watch Cases. (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Deming and Gundlach, 188-?; Card in the shape of a keystone advertising Keystone Watch Cases. (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Deming House, 1881; Hotel was located in Niantic, but address on card is "Hartford, Conn.", where there was apparently an office. (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Business card, Designer Fabrics and Interiors, 198-?; Athena A. Economou, Proprietor (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Postcard, J.C. Dexter Photo Co., 19--; "Special Photographs for Christmas" (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Mrs. J.L. Dickerson, 18--; "Books and Stationery, Toys and Fancy Good, Cigars, Tobacco, Confectionery, Circulating Library, Employment Office…. Collars, Cuffs and Gents Furnishing Goods, and other articles too numerous to mention." (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, F.P. Dickinson and Company, 1880; Four different designs. Copyright 1880 by Bufford, Boston (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, DiFiore of Hartford, 1987; Don Difiore, Owner Chef; Colleen Difiore, Owner Manager (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Charles Dillon and Company, 1914 (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Direct Importing Company, 19--; Card features a photograph of "Our Coffees" (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, E.B. Dix, 188-?; Two cards in the shape of fans with oriental designs (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, E.B. Dix, 1880?; "Successor to Charles R. Dix" (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, E.B. Dix, 188-?; Six different designs, five with birds, one with a seascape (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, E.B. Dix, 188-?; Thirteen different designs with girls repesenting the nations of the world (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Blotter, Do-More Seating Service, 195-?; "William A. Rice for Do/More Seating." (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Domestic Sewing Machine Company, 1883; Two different designs, one with a horse, the other with a courting couple (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Domestic Sewing Machine Company, 188-?; Design features girl with cat and book with a picture of a sewing machine (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Domestic Sewing Machine Company, 188-?; "The Model Machine" "It Stands at the Head" (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Dow Brothers, 1878?; "Save frp, 50c to $1 per bbl." (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Dow Brothers, 1878; Floral design (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Louise E. Dunlap, 1880; "Scenes of Childhood" copyrighted, Bufford, Boston. (Box 8, Folder D)
  - Trade card, Eagle Dye House, 189-?; George Rohrmayer, Proprietor (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, Eagle Dye Works Company, 193-?; "Gentlemen: Please have your representative call for….. Wearing Apparel, Draperies, Rugs." (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, A.J. Eastman, 18--?; "All work will be done in a First Class Manner, and at Reasonable Prices." (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, Edward B. Eaton, 1907; "I realize the great value of the Original Photographs taken on the Battlefields durng the Civil War by Matthew B. Brady, Government Photographer, and I should like to see this Historic Collection published in Albums at a cost as low as $2.00…." (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, J.H. Eckhardt and Company, 188-; "Fine Arts Suitable for Holiday Presents." Two different designs. (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, J.W. Eldridge, 187-; "A Perfect Fit at the Boston Shoe Store." Card in the shape of a shoe. (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, R.S. Eldridge, 188-?; "Plated Ware, Fine Jewelry, Boss Pat. Cases." (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, R.S. Eldridge, 1889-1890; "I bought my spectacles of R. S. Eldridge." Two designs featuring cats wearing eyeglasses (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, Elias Glass Company, 194-?; "Ready to Serve You with All Flat Glass Items. Manufacturer of Mirrors." (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, Elite Restaurant, 188-?; E. Habenstein, Proprietor. Card in the shape of an artist's palette. (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Bookmark, Henry Ensign and Son, 1881; "Henry Ensign & Son, Clothiers, Have Removed from 174 to 68 State Street, Courant Building, Hartford, March 1st, 1881." (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Postcard, L.L. Ensworth and Son, 1899; "Agent for Wm. Jessop & Son's Best Cast Steel." (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Advertisement, L.L. Ensworth and Son, ca. 1900; Two different copies of "Little Tots Drawing Book" with advertisement for L. L. Ensworth and Son on the back. (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, Exchange Hotel, 185-?; C. A. Colton, Proprietor. "A Strictly Temperance House." (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, A. Estlow, 188-?; "Try A. Estlow's new 5c. Cigar, Merry Bachelors." (Box 8, Folder E)
  - Trade card, Fairman and Henry, 188-?; "Successors to Fairman & Miller." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Fairman and Henry, 188-?; Two designs featuring little girls at play (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Fairman and Henry, 188-?; "S. D. Sollers & Co's Celebrated Fine Shoes & Slippers… For Sale by Fairman & Miller…" Two different comic designs (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Fairman and Henry, 188-?; "Light Expenses - Small Profits" (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Fairman and Henry, 188-?; Landscape design (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, E.B. Farnham, 186-?; "Lehigh, Lackawanna, Wilkesbarre, Franklin [Coal] The best in the world." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Farren Brothers, 188-?; Five different cards in the shape of fans (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Farren Brothers, 1880; Four cards with different triangular designs. Copyright 1880 by F. Todd (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Farren Brothers, 188-?; Eleven cards with children representing the Months of the Year. Captions in French. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Postcard, Fay Battery Copany, 192-?; "Dear Sir: Your Storage Battery is Ready…." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Farren Brothers, 188-?; Four cards with children playing. "Guarantee Rolling Spring Bed." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Brochure, Linus T. Fenn, 189-?; "All Kinds of Furniture embracing Parlor Suits, Chamber Suits, Hall, Library, Dining Room and Kitchen Furniture." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Linus T. Fenn, 189-?; "Assortment the Largest, Prices the Lowest." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Postcard, Fisk Rubber Company, 191-?; "We Carry a Complete Stock of All Styles and Sizes." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Fisk's Popular Shoe Store, 1885?; Three designs showing children at play. "Why Not Save Money When You Can?" (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Fisk's Popular Shoe Store, 1885?; Three designs featuring birds. "Save Your Money!" "Boots & Shoes at prices hitherto unknown in Hartford." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Envelope, J.D. Fiske and Company, 189-; "Patented Sept. 23, 1890." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Business card, Wayne fleming Photo Studio, 198-?; "Commercial and Industrial Photography." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Postcard, Flint-Bruce Company, 1910-1912; Nine different postcards depicting interiors of rooms furnished by the Flint-Bruce Company (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, John Flynn, before 1914; Image of dollar bill on back of card. Printed by Bufford, Boston. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 1898-1899; "Nobby Children's Suits." Two designs featuring girls in interiors. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 1898-1899; "Visit the New England Combination Clothiers and Hatters." Two designs featuring children sledding (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 1898-1899; "Great Markdown Bargain Sale." Two copies of a card with goldfinches. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 1898-1899; "Always Go To A. L. Foster & Co." Card featuring children at the beach. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 1898-1899; "For a Complete Assortment of Holiday Goods visit A. L. Foster & Co." Winter scene with three children (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 1882?; "Nobby and Attractive Styles in New Fall Hats." Two designs featuring children and flowers. Printed by Charles Taber & Co., New Bedford, Mass. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 189-?; "Low One-Price Cash Clothiers." Two designs with children sailing an eggshell at the beach. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 189-?; The Reliable and Stylish Low One-Price Cash Clothiers." Three designs with seasonal landscapes. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 189-?; "Low One-Price Cash Clothiers." Comic design featuring an African-American woman. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 1898-1899; "Operate 27 Stores in New England." Large card with photograph of a woman (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 189-?; "The Low One Price Cash Clothiers." Two designs with comic couples (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.L. Foster and Company, 189-?; Four different designs (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Fowler and Sans Souci, 188-?; "Ladies' & Gents Fine Shoes." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Fox and Company, 1880?; Four designs featuring costumed figures (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Dudley Fox, 188-; "Watches, Clocks and Jewelry, Solid Silver and Plated Ware, Spectacles and Eye-Glasses." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Business card, G. Fox, 198-?; Business card of Sandra Wilson, Interior Decorating Studio (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Membership card, G. Fox, 198-?; Membership card in G. Fox Hosiery Club Frequent Buyer Club (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Postcard, G. Fox, 1991; "Thanks for…. Your support throughout 1991." Eugene S. Kahn, President; John L. Dunham, Chairman (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Fowler and Griswold, 186-?; A. J. Fowler and H. Griswold, Proprietors (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Fowler and Hunting Company, 196-? (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, S. Frankenfield, 188-?; Two different designs with winged children and butterflies (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Frank's Restaurant, Inc., 197-?; Frank Parseliti, Proprietor. "Hartford's Finest Continental, American and Italian Restaurant" (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, F.L. French and Company, 18-?; "Manufacturer of Harness, New York Style--of superior quality…. " (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Business card, S.I. Freeman, 193-?; Business card of J. W. Church (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, S.I. Freeman, 19--?; "L. E. Church with S. I. Freeman, Wholesale and Retail Dealer in Ready Made Clothing." 2 copies. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, S.I. Freeman, 187-?; "The People are Pleased with What They Buy at Freeman's Clothing Bazaar…" Two different comic designs. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, S.I. Freeman, 187-?; "Finest Clothing at the Lowest Prices" (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, S.I. Freeman, 187-?; "All Ready for the Fall & Winter Campaign!" (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Freeman One-Price Clothier, 187-?; "First Clothing Store from Main St." Three comic designs. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Freeman's One-Price Clothing Bazar, 187-?; Four different designs featuring cats (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Freeman's One-Price Clothing Bazar, 187-?; "Closing Out Sale, in order to make room for the winter stock." (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Freeman's One-Price Clothing Bazar, 187-?; "First Store from Main Street. Four seasonal landscapes (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, Freeman's One-Price Clothing Bazar, 187-?; Six miscellaneous designs (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Postcard, Fuller Brush Company, 192-?; Three different advertising postcards, one dated 1928. (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Trade card, A.B. Fuller, 188-?; Two different designs printed by Ketterlinus, Philadelphia (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Postcard, C.C. Fuller Company, 1914; Postcard with calendar and view of interior of a bedroom (Box 9, Folder F)
  - Postcard, Gallup and Metzger, 1888?; Large card with portrait of the opera singer Adeline Patt (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Postcard, Gallup and Metzger, 189-?; Agents for Wm. Knabe & Company and Haines Pianos; two different designs (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Postcard, Gallup and Metzger, 189-?; "See the Haines Brothers Upright Piano." Two different designs featuring women. (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Postcard, Gallup and Metzger, 189-?; Two large cards with pictures of children. "Every Piano fully warranted for five years." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Postcard, Gallup and Metzger, 189-?; "Pianos, organs, Sheet Music and Musical Merchandise." "Representing Haines Bros. and other Celebrated Manufacturers." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, P. Garvan, 188-?; "All Kinds of Paper Made to Order at Manufacturers' Prices." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, E. Gately and Company, 19--?; "General House Furnishings. Credit Given." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Geeley, 1880-1885; Four different designs (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Geeley the Clothier, 1880-1885; One comic design: "Searching for Tulips." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Geeley Wardrobe, 188-?; "Mens', Youth's and Boy's Clothing." Design featuring two men. (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Geeley Wardrobe, 188-?; "Mens', Youth's and Boy's Clothing." Two designs featuring two children. (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Geeley Wardrobe, 188-?; Design features a hunter and four owls (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Geeley Wardrobe, 188-?; "The best assortment of Men's, Youths' and Boys' Clothing." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Elihu Geer, 18--?; "Printing of all kinds, with dispatch, promptness, and at low prices." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Elihu Geer, 19--; "Annual Town Reports; Assessors' Tax Lists, Abstract Sheets & Books; also Collector's Pocket Tax Books…." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Business card, E. Howard Geer, 189-?; "Engineer's Yeoman 'U.S.S. Wachusett' 1864-1868" (Box 9, Folder G)